【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 18]
[第18集]
It would be better if Hong Zao was here
要是洪早在就好了
You can keep each other company.
你们可以互相陪伴。
This horse is very obedient.
这匹马很听话。
Tomorrow I will teach you how to ride...
明天我教你怎么骑…
sorry.
对不起。
I'm not the person you want to see
我不是你想见的人
Why come if you know you're not welcome?
如果你知道自己不受欢迎，为什么还要来？
Do you think I'm deaf and blind and don't understand anything?
你以为我又聋又瞎， 什么都不懂吗？
i came here
我来到这里
Talk to you, if I can.
和你谈谈，如果可以的话。
Chengbi, you are actually a mute, right?
橙碧，你其实是个哑巴吧？
My ex didn’t talk much;
前任话不多，
Almost like a mute.
几乎就像一个哑巴。
He goes home to visit his family
他回家探望家人
and never came back,
并且再也没有回来，
It's like he never existed.
就好像他从未存在过一样。
Were you the one who killed Mr. Song?
宋大人是你杀的吧？
Thank God.
感谢上帝。
I hope he dies.
我希望他死。
There are knife marks there
那里有刀痕
On Master Song's carriage.
宋爷的马车上。
Not many people in the capital use blades.
首都使用刀片的人并不多。
As for your blade,
至于你的刀片，
When you decide to use a blade
当你决定使用刀片时
Qingxing asked me to design it as a gift.
庆星让我设计它作为礼物。
I've modified it so it will be more
我已经修改了它，所以它会更多
It's suitable for women and I can recognize it.
适合女人用， 我也能认得出来。
My spies near the Prince Regent's residence have reported
我在摄政王府邸附近的间谍报告了
Someone broke into the mansion tonight.
今晚有人闯入宅邸。
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
He's yours too, isn't he?
也是你的人，不是吗？
what do you want?
你想要什么？
Arrest me like before?
像以前一样逮捕我？
if i want to do this
如果我想这么做的话
I did this a long time ago.
我很久以前就这么做了。
Are you playing with me?
那你是在玩我吗？
do you like seeing me
你喜欢见到我吗
Acting like a clown?
表现得像个小丑？
If this is the case,
如果是这样，
There's no harm in killing you.
杀了你也没什么坏处。
He Jiuling, don’t you understand yet?
何九菱，你还没明白吗？
No matter what you want to do, I can help you.
无论你想做什么，我都可以帮助你。
help me?
帮我？
Your family is like Master Zhongyong’s watchdog . help me?
你的家人就像忠雍大人的看门狗一样 。帮我？
I am not my family
我不是我的家人
I'm not a regent either.
我也不是摄政王的人。
I'm just myself.
我只是我自己。
I just want to atone for my sins.
我只是想赎回我的罪过。
do it.
做吧。
Why did you stop?
你为什么停下了？
Do you think I'm scared?
你觉得我害怕吗？
you know too.
你也知道。
Whether it's you, me, or anyone else,
无论是你、我、还是其他人，
At that time none of us had the ability
那时我们谁都没有能力
We can't change the outcome,
我们也无法改变结果，
we can?
我们能？
Master, where are you going?
少爷，你要去哪里？
Master, it's getting dark. where are you going?
少爷，天黑了。你要去哪里？
I can send someone to escort you.
我可以派人护送你。
unnecessary.
不需要。
Don't bother, Your Highness.
不用费心，殿下。
I can take care of the young master.
我可以照顾少爷。
Not bad, but it's too late
也还好，不过已经晚了
There may be tigers and wolves outside the tent.
帐篷外可能有老虎和狼。
You should be careful.
你应该小心。
I want to see
我想看看
Who wants to take my life away.
谁想要夺走我的生命。
Why are you here alone in the middle of the night?
你怎么 大半夜一个人在这儿？
What if something happens?
如果发生什么事怎么办？
My eyes are a bit red, aren't they?
我的眼睛有点红，不是吗？
Maybe I'm just tired.
也许我只是累了。
this late,
这么晚了，
Then let's go back and rest.
那么我们回去休息吧。
Tomorrow we must go to the hunting ground.
明天我们必须去狩猎场。
tomorrow,
明天，
Don't go to the hunting grounds.
不要去狩猎场。
Did you forget it?
你忘了吗？
The emperor gave me a bow and arrow
皇帝赐给我弓箭
And said he wanted to see me shoot a wild boar.
并说他想看我射杀一头野猪。
Don't go.
别走。
Alright alright.
好吧好吧。
Do you want me to fly a kite with you?
你要我和你一起放风筝吗？
Then I will fly a kite with you tomorrow
那我明天先和你一起放风筝
I'll teach you how to ride a horse. The day after tomorrow I will...
我会教你如何骑马。 后天我会……
Don’t go the day after tomorrow either.
后天也别去。
Rong Yu, you...what's wrong with you?
容羽，你……你怎么了？
I'm not sure myself.
我自己也不太确定。
But can you not go?
但你能不去吗？
You haven't told me yet,
你还没告诉我，
Why are you here alone?
你为什么一个人在这里？
I'm afraid of uncle
我害怕叔叔
If he knew he would be angry with you
如果他知道的话他会生你的气
You run around.
你到处乱跑。
He is an elder.
他是一位长辈。
if he is angry with me
如果他对我生气
I won't take it seriously.
我不会放在心上。
Your family is my family.
你的家人就是我的家人。
I will be nice to him
我会对他好
I will try to make him forgive me.
我会努力让他原谅我。
Good morning, Master.
早上好，少爷。
The lady said,
女士说，
You stay up late and look at her before going to bed,
你熬夜 睡觉前看着她，
So she told me not to wake you up.
所以她叫我不要叫醒你。
Where is she now?
她现在在哪儿？
She was just called over
她刚刚被叫过来
The lady of the main palace,
主殿的小姐，
Now she should be called Princess Xihe.
现在应该叫羲和公主了。
Master.
少爷。
Ms. Rong.
容女士。
Why don't you play a tune?
你为什么不演奏一首曲子呢？
Sorry, I don't know what to do.
抱歉，我不知道该怎么办。
If nothing else
如果没有别的事情的话
I'll take my leave first
我先告辞了
wait,
等待，
As a noble lady of the Jialin family,
作为嘉琳世家的贵妇，
I don’t even understand this most basic skill
连这个最基本的技能都不懂
It's so embarrassing.
实在是太丢人了。
Our ancestor emperor established a school for girls,
我们的祖先皇帝 建立了一所女子学校，
Enable girls to become proficient in poetry, music, and piano.
使女孩子能精通 诗、乐、琴。
Ms. Rong.
容女士。
You couldn't draw before.
以前你不会画画。
Now you can't play the guzheng.
现在你不能弹古筝了。
You have to be able to do something.
你必须能够做某事。
Poetry, song, painting, music, and pipa art.
诗、歌、画、乐、 琵琶艺术。
I can't do any of these things.
这些事情我都做不了。
So if there is any related incident
所以如果有任何相关事件的话
Don't bother inviting me.
不用费心邀请我。
If you don't know how, you can learn.
如果你不会，你可以学习。
The face of a woman before she gets married is the face of her father and brothers.
女人 出嫁前的脸就是父亲和兄弟的脸。
And after getting married, it becomes the face of the husband's family.
而结婚后，更是婆家的面子。
Playing with swords is not something that can be shown on the stage.
玩剑不是 舞台上可以呈现的。
Do you think you will be drafted into war in the future?
你觉得你 以后会被征召上战场吗？
Since you live in the capital,
既然你住在首都，
At the ladies' party
在贵妇小姐的聚会中
If there is nothing you can do,
如果你无能为力，
Don't you look like -
你难道不会看起来——
Like a fool?
像一个傻瓜？
Try to twist Mrs. Rong's hand a little.
试着稍微扭一下容太太的手。
She was disabled for a while before her marriage.
结婚前她曾有一段时间残疾。
I wonder if she can still play the guzheng.
不知道她还能不能弹古筝。
If she can, I, as a princess, will definitely help her.
如果她可以的话，我作为公主一定会帮助她。
After the hunting trip, I will arrange for her to study
狩猎之旅结束后， 我会安排她学习
and my six or seven year old cousin.
和我六七岁的表弟。
Poetry, song, painting, music, pipa art
诗、歌、画、乐、 琵琶艺术
Like swords and clubs,
就像剑、棍棒一样，
Spears, axes, hooks and forks.
矛、斧头、钩子和叉子。
There is no difference in their value.
它们的价值没有区别。
What kind of person does a woman want to be?
女人想成为什么样的人
Who is criticizing.
是由谁来批评的。
As for the face of my father and my husband’s family,
至于父亲 和婆家的面子，
Why don't they make their own money?
他们为什么不自己挣钱
But is it up to you?
但靠你来做吗？
What will we do?
我们会做什么？
They immediately started fighting.
他们立即开始战斗。
indeed.
的确。
they do not
他们没有
It was very honorable yesterday.
昨天很有面子。
Others deliberately let you win.
别人故意让你赢。
Did they do it?
他们做了吗？
What?
什么？
Let it go, I'm a princess now.
放手吧，我现在是公主了。
I dare you to disrespect me.
我敢说你不尊重我。
Yesterday I told them what dignity means.
昨天我告诉他们尊严意味着什么。
It means don't be arrogant and make others uncomfortable.
意思是不要 傲慢地让别人不舒服。
If you don't understand this,
如果你不明白这一点，
I wouldn't mind teaching you again.
我不介意再教你一次。
Just like you taught me how to play guzheng today.
就像你今天教我 弹古筝一样。
let go. Let me go.
松手。让我走。
Mrs. Rong, you...
容太太，你……
I just want to drink tea alone with Miss Jiang
我只想和江小姐单独喝茶
Solve the problem
解决问题
She is always unhappy to see me.
她总是不高兴见到我。
If you want to play the guzheng, come on.
如果你想弹古筝，就来吧。
I…
我…
how…
如何…
I advise you to behave yourself.
我劝你还是规矩点吧。
In front of so many people,
当着这么多人的面，
Don't lose your dignity as a princess.
不要失去作为公主的尊严。
wait.
等待。
The emperor and regent are here.
皇帝和摄政王都在这里。
He Jiuling wouldn't do anything to her.
贺九菱不会对她做什么。
But if you offend her
但如果你得罪了她
She definitely won't mind
她绝对不会介意
Create a scene for others to laugh at.
制造场面让别人笑话。
Chengbi.
Chengbi.
She drank some hallucinogenic tea,
她喝了一些含有致幻剂的茶，
But the effect only lasts for one stick of incense.
但效果只持续 一炷香的时间。
I'll be back in time.
我会及时回来的。
Keep an eye on her.
留意她。
Be careful.
当心。
Master.
少爷。
Why are you so anxious to find her?
你为什么这么着急找她？
The place is full of women.
这个地方到处都是女人。
Master Rong.
荣师傅。
Let's not stay here, okay?
我们不要留在这里，好吗？
Isn't this Master Rong?
这不是容师傅吗？
Master, what might happen to your lady?
少爷， 夫人可能会出什么事？
Master.
少爷。
Master Rong.
荣师傅。
Is Mr. Rong looking for He Jiuling?
容老爷子是在找贺九菱吗？
He Jiuling and Princess Xihe
He Jiuling and Princess Xihe
Has been gone for a while.
已经消失有一段时间了。
Master, Master.
少爷，少爷。
Master, where are you going?
少爷，你要去哪里？
Master.
少爷。
wait.
等待。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Your Highness,
殿下，
Your Majesty gave you a new horse today,
陛下今日赐予一匹新马，
The young master also comes to try it.
小少爷也来尝试一下。
Try horses?
试试马？
Master,
少爷，
This is a hunting ground.
这是一个狩猎场。
There are wild animals around,
周围有野兽出没，
The sword has no eyes.
剑没有眼睛。
I don't want you to get hurt.
我不想让你受伤。
Master, Master.
少爷，少爷。
It's noisy.
太吵了。
For your safety,
为了你的安全，
I will send someone to take you back.
我会派人送你回去。
Servants!
仆人们！
Yesterday, His Majesty granted me a new position.
昨天，陛下 授予我一个新职位。
so what?
所以呢？
It's higher than yours.
它比你的高。
Your Highness.
殿下。
Can you slow down a little?
你能慢一点吗？
My master is not a skilled rider,
我的主人不是熟练的骑手，
He could barely keep up.
他几乎跟不上。
Your Highness, why did you stop?
殿下，你为何停下来？
My master's Turkish horse could hardly move.
我主人的土耳其马几乎不能动了。
Your Highness,
殿下，
Why are you running so fast again?
你怎么又跑这么快了？
My master couldn't keep up.
我的主人跟不上。
The Prince Regent is back.
摄政王回来了。
I'm here to count the games for His Highness.
我是来给殿下数比赛的。
Just now, several lords came back
刚刚，几位领主回来了
There are only a few chickens.
只有几只鸡。
And His Majesty also had a great time.
而且陛下也玩得很开心。
I have nothing here, go away.
我这里什么都没有，滚吧。
Wipe your drool.
擦干你的口水。
I'm not drooling. You are fooling me.
我没有流口水。你在愚弄我。
Well, I must have read it wrong.
嗯，一定是我看错了。
Sorry, I fell asleep while I was scolding you.
对不起，我骂你的时候睡着了。
However, judging from your situation
不过，从你的情况来看
sincerely apologize,
真诚的道歉，
I don't blame you just yet.
我暂时不会责怪你。
This is the illusion you see.
这就是你看到的幻象。
What did you say?
你说什么？
there is nothing.
没有什么。
Cheng Bi, let’s go.
程碧，我们走吧。
She was scolded severely by me just now.
刚才她被我狠狠地骂了一顿。
Why does a paper tiger act so tough?
一个纸老虎，为何要表现得如此强硬？
So refreshing.
太清爽了。
Why am I here?
为什么我在这里？
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
slower.
慢一点。
I don't run.
我不跑步。
Rong Yu, be careful not to fall.
容羽，小心别摔倒了。
where have you been?
你去哪儿了？
I just had tea with the ladies.
我只是和女士们一起喝茶。
Nothing to worry about, right?
没什么可担心的，对吧？
Really?
真的吗？
What? Do not you trust me?
什么？你不相信我吗？
Instead, you're running around all day.
相反，你整天都在奔波。
Do you know how dangerous this is?
你知道这有多危险吗？
Forget it, I'll find another chance later.
算了，以后再找机会。
Jiuling, come back and sleep.
九龄，回来睡觉吧。
Do you want this?
你想要这个吗？
how about this?
这个怎么样？
Eat more of this
多吃点这个吧
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
Do you know how angry I get these days?
你知道 我这些天有多生气吗？
I don't know what to do with you.
我不知道该拿你怎么办。
Frankly speaking.
坦白地说。
Are you sent by God to punish me?
你是上天派来惩罚我的吗？
Have some tea.
喝点茶。
Follow the regent all day long,
整天跟着摄政王，
are not you tired?
你不累吗？
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
there is nothing.
没有什么。
What's there to argue with you?
有什么好和你争论的？
Let’s order more food
再来点菜吧
This Li Yuhan still dares to play the piano?
这个李昱寒还敢弹琴？
Everyone was gossiping the day before yesterday
前天 大家都在八卦
She plays the piano out of tune,
她的琴弹得不合拍，
She should restrain here, lift there.
她应该 在这里克制，那里举起。
so embarrassing
太尴尬了
She puts on her best face
她摆出一副最棒的样子
Look down on everyone.
看不起所有人。
Finally someone looked down on her.
终于有人看不起她了。
Exactly.
确切地。
Speaking of which,
说到这，
Mr. Rong’s piano skills
容公子的琴艺
All extremely beautiful.
都异常美丽。
It's a pity now.
现在很可惜。
it's a pity.
真可惜。
Have some tea.
喝点茶。
Have you ever played guzheng before?
你以前弹过古筝吗？
Are you talking about what we're hearing now?
你说的是我们现在听到的吗？
I think she sounds horrible.
我觉得她听起来很可怕。
She even missed some notes.
她甚至漏掉了一些笔记。
Maybe I'll do better.
也许我会做得更好。
Even if you can,
即使你可以，
I don’t know when I’ll actually hear it.
我不知道什么时候我才能真正听到它。
Master, madam.
少爷，夫人。
During these days of hunting,
在这几天的狩猎过程中，
Your Majesty got some good stuff
陛下得到了一些好东西
and are distributing them.
并正在分发它们。
Everyone else is gone, but you are nowhere to be seen
别人都走了，你 却不见踪影
So I've been sent to invite you to claim your reward.
所以我被派去邀请你 来领取你的奖励。
thank you, sir.
谢谢你，先生。
sorry. I've never been able to get a military badge.
对不起。我一直没能 获得军事标志。
This wasn't supposed to be an easy task.
这本来不应该是一件容易的事。
Apart from,
除了，
Everyone else was looking at the Regent's Palace.
其他人都在注视着摄政王府。
Master,
少爷，
Isn't this bunny cute?
这只兔子是不是很可爱？
Look, it's been hungry for a while.
瞧，它已经饿了一段时间了。
Come on, come on, feed it quickly.
来来来，赶紧喂它吧。
Watchers outside the Prince Regent's palace
摄政王府外监视的人
It was sent by Yan Lie.
是炎烈派来的。
I was at the hunting ground a few days ago,
前几天在狩猎场，
He even offered to help me.
他甚至主动提出要帮助我。
In order to stop that old gangster,
为了制止那个老流氓，
I have been supporting the Yan family to fight against him.
我一直在扶植严家 与他作对。
I've egged him on many times
我在他面前怂恿过很多次了
This has made him suspicious of the Yan family.
这已经让他 对严家产生了怀疑。
Steal military signs
窃取军事标志
It had alarmed him.
已经惊动了他。
If he discovers that Yan Lie is spying on the Regent's Palace,
如果他发现严烈正在监视 摄政王府，
Despite Yan Li’s intentions,
尽管严烈有意为之，
The Yan family will be in danger.
严家将会有危险。
it's a pity.
真可惜。
If Your Majesty wants to use Yan Lie,
如果陛下想用颜烈，
After this incident,
这件事情之后，
You can put him under your command.
你可以把他置于你的指挥之下。
But what you hate the most is the Yan family.
但你最讨厌的是严家。
I still.
我仍然。
But I've learned to understand
但我已经学会理解
meaning no choice
别无选择的意思
When things change unpredictably.
当事情发生不可预测的变化时。
I also learned how to survive hatred.
我也学会了如何在仇恨中生存。
Don't push yourself too hard.
不要把自己逼得太紧。
regardless,
无论，
Things are much better now than before.
现在的情况比以前好多了。
I'm counting on you to solve a lot of problems.
我指望你能解决 很多问题。
you must protect yourself
你必须保护自己
And be very careful.
并且要非常小心。
Understood.
明白了。
By the way, He Jiuling,
顺便说一句，何九龄，
Now like this with Rong Yu,
现在和容宇这样，
Isn't this too difficult for you?
这对你来说不是太难了吗？
he?
他？
He might actually be my lucky star.
他实际上可能是我的幸运星。
If you want to leave him in the future
如果以后你想离开他的话
I can help you.
我可以帮你。
When the He family encountered misfortune,
当何家遭遇不幸时，
He saved me from water and fire.
他把我从水和火中救了出来。
I know you are a person who takes kindness seriously.
我知道你是一个 认真对待善良的人。
But also keep this in mind.
但也要把这一点记在心里。
You never know when you'll need it.
你永远不知道什么时候会需要它。
【Rong's Mansion】
【荣氏府邸】
The people from the pharmacy just came over.
刚刚药房的人过来了。
They said they found ambrosia.
他们说他们找到了仙草。
Where?
在哪里？
Outside the city, inside Jingshan Mountain.
城外，荆山内。
That's a long way off.
那是很远的事。
It doesn't matter. No matter how far I have to go.
没关系。 不管有多远我都必须走。
Why can't I see a future for the Regent?
为什么我看不到 摄政王的未来？
Even the stars are blurred.
连星星都模糊了。
There aren't any useful clues.
没有任何有用的线索。
How is this going?
这是怎么回事？
Could it be that there are masters around him who are changing his destiny?
难道他 身边有高手在改变他的命运吗？
I know nothing about this?
我对此一无所知？
Master.
少爷。
It's getting late.
天色已晚。
Don't you need to buy lotus cakes for Madam?
不用给夫人买莲饼吗？
If you don't go now, they'll be sold out.
如果你现在不去，它们就会卖光了。
You came back later than usual today.
今天你比平常回来得晚了一些。
They are still hot.
它们仍然很热。
The future will always be hot.
未来会一直很热。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
I just said it casually.
我只是随口说的。
It tastes better when hot.
热的时候更好吃。
It’s even more delicious than what you like to eat in Xicheng.
比你在西城爱吃的还要好吃。
Isn't it?
不是吗？
Eat more if you like.
喜欢的话就多吃点吧。
By the way, Rong Yu,
顺便说一下，容宇，
I have something to discuss with you.
我有件事要和你商量。
I need to find an herb
我需要找到一种药草
It's called ambrosia.
名为天仙草。
It's freshest after it rains.
下雨后才最新鲜。
So if it rains tonight
所以如果今晚下雨的话
I'm going to Jingshan.
我要去荆山。
This way I can get up early to get the medicine tomorrow.
这样明天我就可以早起 去取药了。
hurry up.
快点。
let's go.
我们走吧。
I brought you some summer clothes.
我给你带了一些夏天的衣服。
If the weather is hot tomorrow
明天天气热的话
Let Zhanping change it for you.
让展平给你改一下。
And this sachet,
还有这个香包，
I just did it,
我刚刚做到了，
And the smell is a bit strong,
而且味道有点重，
But it is used to repel mosquitoes.
但它是用来驱蚊的。
Even if you think it smells bad when you sleep at night,
即使你觉得 晚上睡觉的时候味道很臭，
Never take it off.
永远不要把它脱下来。
I also smoked your quilt with vanilla.
我还用香草熏过你的被子。
How long will you be gone?
你要离开多久？
I'll be back tomorrow night.
我明天晚上就回来。
It's just one day.
这只是一天。
nothing to worry about
没什么可担心的
correct?
正确的？
But I still felt uneasy.
但我还是感到不安。
Then I'll go with you.
那我就跟你一起去吧。
That would make me more worried.
那样我会更担心。
Rong Yu, Rong Yu.
Rong Yu, Rong Yu.
This annoying habit of dragging things out of me
这种讨厌的 把东西从我身上拖出来的习惯
it was all your fault.
都是你的错。
you are too much trouble
你太麻烦了
It's too worrying.
也太令人担忧了。
I've never
我从来没有
Like before.
像以前这样。
My fault.
我的错。
This is. I blame you.
这是。我怪你。
But this time,
但这一次，
Let me go with you.
让我和你一起去吧。
All right. I heard.
好吧。我听到了。
Don't worry, Chengbi and Wu Ritan are by my side.
别担心，城碧和吴日坛都在我身边。
when you come back,
当你回来时，
We will move to another house.
我们将搬到另一所房子。
it seems
它似乎
I have a family again.
我又有了家庭。
Tan, slow down.
谭，慢点。
We have collected all the medicines.
我们已经把药收齐了。
Just because we have it , we are afraid of losing its efficacy.
正因为有了它 ，才怕失去它的功效。
Also, take a look at yourself.
另外，看看你自己。
You obviously want to get back to the city more than anyone else.
你显然 比任何人都更渴望回到城市。
I'll get some water. You guys keep eating
我去拿点水。你们继续吃吧
Keep an eye out for herbs.
留意草药。
These are the Regent's men.
这是摄政王的手下。
Traveling with so few people
带着这么少的人去旅行
It's really too perverted.
实在是太变态了。
After what happened to the Yan family,
严家的事情发生后，
I don't really trust the people
我不太信任人民
All around me now.
现在在我周围。
Who knows when they will betray me?
谁知道他们什么时候会背叛我？
Now the Chen family wants to go to Yanzhou
现在陈家 要求去兖州
Yan State has been demoted to Shu,
燕国已被贬​​蜀，
i have no plan
我没有计划
No more promotion of left and right generals.
不再提拔左右将军。
It's safer to keep everything
保留一切更安全
In my own hands.
在我自己手中。
And, in the hunting grounds,
而且，在狩猎场中，
I had the distinct feeling that someone was trying to hurt me.
我明显感觉到有人 想要伤害我。
The Yan family also began to oppose me frequently.
严家也开始 频繁反对我，
But in the end nothing happened.
但最终什么也没发生。
I really don't know what to do.
我真的不知道该怎么办。
Sir, is it possible that your divination is wrong?
先生，您的占卜有可能是错误的吗？
impossible.
不可能的。
The only mistake was including Rong Yu.
唯一的错误就是把容羽也包括进去了。
This voice...
这个声音……
The fate of people related to astrology is unpredictable.
与占星有关的人的命运 是无法预测的。
His appearance must be
他的外表一定有
Interact with events at the Hunting Ground.
与狩猎场的事件互动。
If I could use a star map
如果我可以使用星图
I will be able to predict more things.
我将能够预测更多的事情。
I understand.
我懂了。
I need to seek more advice from Lord Yung
我需要向容勋爵寻求更多建议
To keep me and my family safe.
以确保我和我家人的安全。
certainly.
当然。
As long as I am regent,
只要我还是摄政王，
Whatever you need, just ask.
无论您需要什么，尽管询问。
Not to mention the He family,
且不说何家，
Even if there are two or three,
即使有两三个，
If they dare stand in my way
如果他们胆敢挡我的路
I will destroy them.
我会消灭他们。
How dare He Jiuling poison my son?
何九龄竟敢毒害我儿子，
I will make the He family pay the price.
我会让何家付出代价。
[Brother and sister-in-law’s grave together]
【兄嫂合墓】
♫ Under the sunset♫
♫ 黄昏夕阳下♫
♫I have traveled thousands of miles♫
♫我行万里路♫
♫Playing the piano under the moonlight♫
♫月光下弹琴♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 饮料不会让我忘记 ♫
♫Write down what I miss you♫
♫写下对你的思念♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫There is no escape from fate♫
♫命运无路可逃♫
♫Looking back, I see you waiting♫
♫回首，我看到你在等待♫
♫Our life is full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Longing to crystallize into a bright galaxy♫
♫ 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河♫
♫You turned around quietly and closed the marriage contract♫
♫你悄悄转身 ，合上婚书♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫问天上有多少颗星星♫
♫Write down what I miss you♫
♫写下对你的思念♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫There is no escape from fate♫
♫命运无路可逃♫
♫Looking back, I see you waiting♫
♫回首，我看到你在等待♫
♫Our life is full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Longing to crystallize into a bright galaxy♫
♫ 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河♫
♫I play the piano gently, waiting for passers-by like you♫
♫我轻轻抚琴， 等待着你这样的路人♫
♫It turns out that you are my inseparable destiny♫
♫原来你是我不可分割的宿命♫